Our game is complete.
我们的游戏已经做好了
Let's build a web player and deploy
让我们把它生成为网页游戏
that web player on to the web.
发布到网页上
Open the Build Settings window.
打开构建设置窗口
The Build Settings has two main sections.
游戏打包的设置主要有两块
The bottom part for setting the build target
底部的部分为设置编译目标
and customising details for the build
以及一些个性化的详细的设置
and the upper part for selecting the
上不是选择打包
scenes to build in to the game.
需要的场景
We do not need to include every scene in our
我们生成游戏的时候不一定需要导入
project when we build our game.
项目中全部的场景
We only need to select the scenes we want.
我们只选定我们需要的场景
We can either drag the scenes we want
我们可以通过吧项目视图中的场景
from our Project view and drop them
拖拽到构建窗口内的上方窗口
in to the upper window
来完成需要导入场景的选定
or we can click the Add Current button
或者我们可以点选Add Current按钮
to add the current open scene to the
这样我们目前打开的场景就会被加入到
build window.
构建窗口
As a side note, we can build a game
这里有一个小知识
with no scenes in the Scenes To Build window.
如果构建窗口中没有场景我们是没办法构建游戏的
If we do this Unity will temporarily use
如果我们这样操作了
the current open scene when building.
Unity会暂时把当前打开的场景打包进游戏
Once we have selected the scenes to build
一旦我们选好了需要打包的场景
it is always good practice to check our
在执行打包操作前检查一下
player settings before we actually build the game.
玩家设置是一个好习惯
For more information on player settings
更多关于玩家设置的信息
please see the information linked below.
请参考下方连接
When we are satisfied with our player settings
当我们调整好了玩家设定
we can return to the Build Settings window
我们可以回到构建设置窗口点选
and choose Build.
Build
Unity will open a dialogue box
Unity会打开一个对话框
prompting us for a name and location
为打包命名和
for our new build.
选择保存的位置
I like to keep the builds associated with
我个人比较喜欢把这个打包
the project, so let's create a new folder
跟这个项目放在一起
to hold our build.
所以让我们新建一个文件夹来存放它
We will create this folder in the root of our
我们会在项目的根层级新建一个文件夹
project along side the assets
它与项目的资源和程序库
library and other default folders.
以及其他默认文件夹并列
It is important to note that this new folder
注意这个新文件夹
should not be placed inside any of
请不要建在
the default folders.
任何默认文件夹的内部
Create a new folder in our project
新建一个新建文件夹
and call it Builds.
命名为Builds
Save the folder.
回车确认生成新文件夹
With the Builds folder selected
在选定Builds 的情况下
let's name our build Space_Shooter.
把我们的打包命名Space_Shooter
We use the underscore here in the name
这里使用下划线作为名字的好处是
as we will be deploying to the web
当这个程序发布到网上的时候
and this name will be part of the web
这个名字可以直接作为游戏的网址
address or URL for the game.
或者URL
Spaces are not recommended in
空格符并不推荐作为
a web address or URL.
网址或者URL的一部分
So we should use an underscore, dash or
所以我们如果作为网页程序使用的时候
other web friendly character instead of
最好使用下划线或者破折号
spaces here when we are creating a web build.
代替空格这样不容易出问题
It should be noted that we could,
这里需要注意的是
if we chose to,
如果我们需要的话
change the name of the HTML file to
我们可以把HTML文件改名为
index.html if appropriate
index.html
to shorten the length of the URL.
这样URL可以更短一些
When we have named our build select Save.
当命名完包的名称点击Save
Unity will now build our player.
Unity会打包我们的程序
And when the build is done
当打包结束的时候
Unity will open the target folder,
Unity会自动打开目标文件夹
in this case our Builds folder,
也就是保存我们打包的目录
revealing the built game.
展示我们打包的游戏
We have built a web player.
我们生成了一个网页游戏
Open the Space_Shooter folder.
打开Space_Shooter文件夹
The web player comes in 2 parts.
这个文件夹有2部分
A Unity 3D file, which contains the data
一个是Unity 3D文件包含了游戏数据
and an HTML file which describes the page
HTML 文件描述了
that will play the game data in a window.
这个网页游戏的页面情况
If we look at the size of these 2 files
如果我们注意一下这2个文件
we can see that the Unity 3D file is the
我们会发现Unity 3D的文件
larger of the 2 as it contains the game data.
更大一些,因为它保存了游戏的数据
If we select and open the HTML file
如果我们点选并打开HTML文件
our operating system will load the HTML file
我们的系统会把HTML文件
in to our default browser.
加载到我们默认的浏览器中
And the game will play in the web page.
这个游戏可以在网页上运行
We are playing this game locally.
我们只是在本地运行这个游戏
To play this game globally we need to
如果我们想在互联网上玩这个游戏
upload it to a web host of some sort.
我们需要把它上传到网络上的服务器中
As an example I am going to upload this
举个例子,我们将把这个文件
via an FTP client to an existing website.
通过FTP 客户端上传到一个已有的网站上
Open an FTP client, select a destination
打开一个FTP客户端
and upload both the HMTL and data files
上传HMTL和数据文件
into the same directory.
到同一个目录
In this case, for ease, I'm going to
在这里为了方便
upload the entire folder containing both files.
我把包含了2个文件的整个文件上传到服务器上
When the files are uploaded open a browser
当文件上传完毕
and use the URL to open a new web page.
打开使用URL打开一个新网页
The data will load from the web
数据会从网上读取过来
and we're playing the game globally.
这样我们就可在全球任何位置玩这个游戏了
Anyone anywhere in the world with access
任何人只要可以连接互联网
to the internet can play our game.
都可以玩我们的这个游戏
Fantastic.
棒极了
Thank you for taking these assignments,
感谢您参与了这些课程
following along and making this game.
一直跟随着制作这个游戏
Please check out the Learn section of Unity's
请查看Unity网站的学习部分
website for more information,
来获得更多的信息
tutorials, assignments and learning materials.
例如教程，任务和学习资料.